<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="change">Change</string>
    <string name="add">Add</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="change_pw">Change Password</string>

    <string name="fields_empty">Fields empty</string>
    <string name="fields_wrong">Fields wrong</string>
    <string name="fields_empty_message">One or more fields are empty!</string>
    <string name="missmatching_pws">Your old password does not match the saved one!</string>
    <string name="internal_error">An internal error occurred!</string>

    <string name="trustednumber_adddialog_titel">Add Trusted Number</string>
    <string name="trustednumber_deldialog_titel">Delete entry?</string>
    <string name="trustednumber_deldialog_message">Do you want to delete this entry?</string>
    <string name="trustednumber_adddialog_name">Name</string>
    <string name="trustednumber_adddialog_number">Number</string>

    <string name="photo_trap_settings">Photo Trap Settings</string>
    <string name="instant_photo_settings">Instant Photo Settings</string>
    <string name="gps_tracking_settings">GPS Tracking Settings</string>

    <string name="gps_tracking">GPS Tracking</string>
    <string name="instant_photo">Instant Photo</string>
    <string name="photo_trap">Photo Trap</string>

    <string name="accept_conditions">I accept the conditions above</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_photo_trap">If you enable the \"Photo Trap\" feature, any person that you added to your trusted contacts and that knows your password will be able to trigger the photo trap via SMS at any time by providing the valid password, for as long as this feature is enabled. A dialog will show up on this device, and take a picture after interacting with the dialog. The picture will be send back to the person that triggered the Photo Trap. By ticking this checkbox, you agree that this app can take and provide photos as requested via SMS with a valid password. You can disable the feature or retract your consent at any time by unchecking this checkbox.</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_instant_photo">If you enable the \"Instant Photo\" feature, any person that you added to your trusted contacts and that knows your password will be able to request a photo via SMS at any time by providing the valid password, for as long as this feature is enabled. By ticking this checkbox, you agree that this app can take and provide photos as requested via SMS with a valid password. You can disable the feature or retract your consent at any time by unchecking this checkbox.</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_tracking">If you enable the \"GPS-position\" feature, any person that you added to your trusted contacts and that knows your password will be able to request the current location of this device via SMS by providing the valid password at any time, for as long as this feature is enabled. By ticking this checkbox, you agree that this app can access and provide GPS information as requested via SMS with a valid password. You can disable the feature or retract your consent at any time by unchecking this checkbox.</string>

    <string name="trap_dialog_title">Shutdown</string>
    <string name="trap_dialog_message">Your device will automatically shut down in 30 seconds!\nPlease confirm to shut down immediately or cancel.</string>
</resources>